sureseats.com 2019-04-07

# Sureseats | Privacy Policy

At Sureseats, we are committed to protecting all the personal information given to us by our guests/clients in the course of our business transactions. We comply with the Data Privacy Act of the Philippines (RA 10173) and make sure that all your personal information are processed in adherence to the general principles of transparency, legitimate purpose and proportionality.

By registering on this site or providing any one of the Sureseats with personal information, you agree to the terms detailed in our Privacy Policy website, and give full consent to the Company to collect, record, organize, store, update, use, consolidate, block, erase or otherwise process information, whether personal, sensitive or privileged, pertaining to yourself and the transactions which are subject hereof and will be used for the implementation of this agreement. These data may be used by Sureseats to provide products and services requested, communicate relevant information and special offers by phone, email or SMS, analyze data for operational improvement, and to comply with legal and regulatory requirements in the interest of public safety and security. Personal data may also be shared among all Sureseats, with access limited to authorized personnel.

Please read the details of our Privacy Policy at <https://www.ayalaland.com.ph/privacy-policy/>

You may withdraw consent at any time to the processing and use of your personal information for marketing purposes by e-mailing us at [admin@sureseats.com](mailto:admin@sureseats.com), using 'Unsubscribe' as the subject line, and providing us with sufficient personal identifiers to enable us to act promptly on the request.

For questions or concerns about our Privacy practices or requests to update personal information, please contact our Data Privacy Officer at [dataprivacy@sureseats.com](mailto:dataprivacy@sureseats.com) or write to the Ayala Malls Cinemas Office: 3rd Floor, Glorietta 3, Ayala Center, Makati City, Philippines.
